http://www.parkdesigns.net/privacy-policy

Home / Privacy Policy | Park Designs & Split P
Our Privacy PolicyAt Park Designs, we respect your privacy and are committed to maintain and use this information responsibly. We collect information about you through our website in an effort to improve your shopping experience and to communicate with you about our products, services, contests and promotions. This privacy policy addresses the use and disclosure of personal information we collect from you. By visiting our website, and providing your information to us, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy.How we use this informationIn general, we may use information that we collect about you to:deliver the products and services that you have requested;manage your account and provide you with customer support;perform research and analysis about your purchase of, or interest in, our products; communicate with you by email, postal mail, telephone and/or mobile devices about products or service that may be of interest to you from us or other third parties;authorize and verify your eligibility for a wholesale account; enforce our terms and conditions;manage our business andperform functions as otherwise described to you at the time of collection.Park Designs will never sell or market your personal information to other organizations.Your online accountWhen setting up an online account, you will be prompted to select a password. The retrieval of personal information relating to you and your order history is only available to you if you provide the correct password that you have created. All profile information is only available while you are logged into your account.If you forget your password, a new password will be assigned to you and will be emailed to your email address. SecurityThe security of your information is very important to us. We use Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology to protect the security of your online order information. SSL technology encrypts your order information, preventing unauthorized users from viewing your account information.Email: customerservice@parkdesigns.netPhone: 800-326-3382
